ああ　間違いなさそうだ。 動画も添付されてる ターゲットは２人 男女のカップルだ。 俺も　そっちに向かうから 現地で合流しよう。
To become kings, the Chimera Ants
have spread across the world, committing acts of utmost
tyranny wherever they go.
どうやって あの２人を捕まえるかだが…。 無理だね。 ん？ 俺達の手に負える相手じゃないよ。
Infiltration x And x Selection
あれから数年経ってるし 何とかなるかなとは思ったけど…。
Sneaking in was easy. But the question is how to get
close enough to the enemy.
あそこに　ヒソカが２人座ってると 考えたら　少しは分かるか？
And we can't let just anyone see us, either.
確かに　そりゃ 俺らの手に負えそうもねえわな。
This country has a powerful
information regulation system that operates in secret using groups of informants. Informants?
で　あいつら なぜ　ここにいると思う？
Yeah, if you discover an enemy spy,
you receive a reward.
そりゃ　お前　デートだろ　当然。 えっ　そうなの？
If you find evidence of insurgency,
you receive a reward.
違う　あいつら　後ろのカップルにも ちゃんと気づいてたぜ。
If you stop someone from fleeing the
country, you receive a reward. So the people will do anything for that reward.
さりげなく周囲の様子や動きに 細心の注意を払ってる
And they aren't just after money.
初めは マフィアに追われてんだから 注意すんのは 当然かと思ってたけど
After racking up enough informant points,
the entire group is promoted.
それなら初めっから 人目につく広場なんかに 来るわけないんだよね。 あいつらに　追われてる自覚なんか これっぽっちもない。
But if someone provides false information
or a member commits a crime, the entire group is punished. Carrot and stick, huh?
獲物が引っかかるのを 待ってんのさ。
Family members are put in different groups.
狩る気　満々だよ。 見られてんな。 素人じゃないね。
So if an entire group tries to escape, the other family members can be
executed or imprisoned for life.
鎖野郎かね？
If a family is caught trying to escape together,
they'll be executed, no questions asked.
さぁな もし　そうなら団長の命令通り やりたいようにやるだけだ。
For this country's elite to live the good life, the rest of its citizens must scrape by.
団長は恐らく　そいつを 仲間にしたがってると思うけど。 マチ…。
But the media also spreads lies.
Such as that, in other countries, half the population starves by age ten.
団長は２人で鎖野郎を捜し出し 連れて来いとしか言ってねえ。
Foreign aid never reaches the needy.
「生死は問わず　手段は好きに」 そうだろうが。
It's even said that East Gorteau spends
grant money developing nuclear weapons
おめぇが勝手に　団長の意図を 解釈するのは構わねえが
that become bargaining chips in negotiations
for unprecedented foreign aid increases.
それを俺に押しつけんのは やめろ。
Hey, don't overheat!
私は　まだ何も言ってない。
I th-think I'm okay...
てめぇの意見を押しつけてんのは あんただろ。
That was just so complicated...
明らかに　空気　変わったな。 すごい　嫌な感じ。
My brother told me everything. And he probably heard it from Grandpa.
まさか　バレたか？ 大丈夫　気づかれてないよ。 分かんねえだろ 特に俺は　お前らと違って
Your grandpa? Yeah. Long ago, he infiltrated
the country for a job.
「絶」とかいう 気配絶ちなんて　できねえし。
And I've seen similar information
on Hunter websites.
今ここで　んなことしたら 逆に不自然だっつうの。
The system is likely still in use.
もっと自然に朗らかに。
There's a village.
エヘヘ…。 エヘヘ…。
Yeah... It's not very big.
ごめん　俺が悪かった。
What do we do? Sneak in.
今　ここで決めようぜ ルールに沿って
Is that a good idea? We need current information.
生かして連れて行くか 殺して連れて行くかをよ。
Knowing what kinds of clothes they wear or
how to identify someone's rank will help.
いいだろう。
They may have certain practices to root out spies.
表。
The more data we have, the better.
裏。
Wait here.
なるほど おおよそのことは分かった。
It's completely deserted...
部屋を替えたのは賢明だったな。
Maybe everyone already left for Peijing?
「幻影旅団」が プロハンターサイトを利用しているのは
No, something happened here.
まず間違いない 手を打つのが遅れれば
And someone's trying to hide it. Huh?
ネオンに危害が及んだかもしれん 礼を言う。 で　今後のことだが まず　娘は家に帰すことにする。
They did a sloppy job.
オークションは　来年も その次もあるさ　気を落とすな。
They didn't dig deep enough,
so wild dogs got to the bodies.
それに お前が欲しがっていた物は 必ず　パパが 盗賊から取り戻してみせる。
I'd imagine the entire village is buried here.
ホント？
What's going on?
ああ　約束だ　パパがネオンとの 約束を破ったことあったか？ 守ったことのほうが 少ないくせに。
This is the true purpose of
the national celebration. It's a pretense for entire populations of towns
and cities to vanish without raising suspicion.
ハハハ… こりゃ　一本取られたなぁ。
The selection has already begun.
センリツとバショウといったかな？ はっ。 今すぐネオンを連れて 屋敷まで戻ってくれ。
In hindsight, it would be tough to summon all citizens to
the capital and make the selection so quickly.
念のため　不自然でない程度の 変装はしておけよ。
This nation has a population
of around five million.
あぁ…。 それじゃあ　ネオン 部屋に戻って支度をしなさい。
Clearing out one town or city
at a time is more effective.
はい！
In that case, their only concern would
be coworkers or family members
オークションは 今夜から再開されるそうだ。 場所も時間も同じだ。
But with the pretext of the national celebration, no one will find it strange that
they can't contact someone.
コミュニティーにしてみれば 相手が誰だろうが ナメられるわけには いかんのだろう。 「十老頭」は盗まれた品も 必ず取り戻すと言ってる。
In this nation, cell phones aren't allowed, so if they believe the other party is traveling,
it makes sense that they can't contact them.
「盗まれた」？
The selection will go very smoothly.
先程お話しした通り 捕らえた大男の話によると 「『陰獣』の１人に先を越されて 盗んでいない」
The capital city, Peijing, is in the southeast corner.
…と言っていましたが？
They only need to attack the farthest
towns first and work their way east.
ああ　そうだったね。 「陰獣」は全員やられたらしい。 え？ ９人までは 遺体を回収したそうだ。 残る１人が 競売品の運搬役をやってる
If each town is told that the government
will assign its people a time to depart, there won't be any problems regarding
communication between towns.
梟って奴だが 恐らく 「旅団」にさらわれたんだろう。
So, by preventing people from meeting
between towns to travel together, they eliminate any cause for commotion.
念能力の怖さは 「十老頭」も十分　承知だ。
But... Hmm? That means
自白させる能力の持ち主がいれば 拷問の必要すらないからな。
they have to run around the nation
to attack all five million citizens. Yeah.
梟が運び出した競売品は 「旅団」に渡ったものとみている。
If one percent survives, that gives
them fifty thousand soldiers.
で　話を戻すが 「陰獣」が全滅したことで
No, I mean before that.
「十老頭」は「旅団」の始末を プロに依頼した。
There are ten... No, nine days left.
プロ？
If you wanted to check five
million people in that time, you'd need a lot of help.
殺しとは　威嚇の手段であって 専門分野じゃ　ない。 ああいう連中が相手なら
Assuming that one Nen user can check ten thousand citizens in ten days...
専門家に任せたほうが 確かに手っ取り早い。
Five hundred Nen users.
これで俺達が何もしなくても
Exactly!
そいつらが 「旅団」を潰してくれるだろう。
You're getting at the fact that there can't
be that many Ants who can use Nen?
だが　これはコミュニティーに 名を売るチャンスだ。
I agree, but it probably isn't that hard.
何も　殺し屋連中だけに 手柄をやる気はない。
They don't need Nen users to check everyone. Huh? Why not?
そこでだ　クラピカ。 その殺し屋のチームに 参加してもらいたい。
They can use manipulation.
分かってるよ。
The power that Chimera Ant used...
動いたぜ　どうする？ 何度も言うけど　戦って勝てる 相手じゃないからな
I'm guessing it can be used
to automate victims or, like Genthru's power, can probably be
used to control multiple people at once.
何とかするさ しなきゃなんねえんだろ。 うん　黙って帰るわけには いかないもんね。
Ordinary humans have aura as well, so the manipulator could force a
victim's aura to concentrate in his fist.
ん…　ＯＫ。 んじゃ 俺の言うことをよく聞いてくれ。
One punch alone could create
an army of fifty thousand.
尾行は　俺とゴンでやる。 こっから先は　絶対　奴らに 見つかっちゃいけないから
While leaving four million, nine hundred
and fifty thousand dead in the process.
すげぇ　ここにいるのに 存在感が　うつろになった
Well, it isn't all bad news.
ゴン　２つ約束を守れ。 奴らに姿を見られたら 尾行は即中止
If my theory is correct, causing a commotion to stop their
selection will be simple.
速やかに場を離れること それ以外にも　俺が　これ以上 追跡不可能と思ったら中止 いいな
We merely have to pop up, take out whoever is being controlled,
and cause a panic.
うん。 中止の合図はコール１回。
Then we just encourage
もちろん　バイブ設定な。
the people who escape to
check on other towns nearby.
もし奴らがバラけたら 女のほうを追う。 レオリオは ゼパイルと連絡をとって 競売を担当してくれ。 分かった。
If the Chimera Ants have sent controlled
puppets, rather than actual Nen users, taking them down will be a cinch.
お前 尾行の経験なんて　ないよな？
We'll just run around, taking them down
one after another, and wreak havoc.
うん　えっとね ハンター試験の時にヒソカを。 マジ!?　バレずにか？
Yeah. The problem is that they'll detect us quickly.
うん　丸１日くらい くっついてたかな？
Once we make our move,
they'll know we're here.
ほぉ　やるじゃないか！ 痛った！　何で殴んの？
If we want to go with the old man's
plan, we should stay hidden.
まっ　それなら　とにかく合格だ。
What do you think?
今　ターゲットが 広場を抜けて小道に入る。
If the selection has already begun, we can't just stand around watching.
[TEL]　バレてなさそう？ 大丈夫だ　「絶」を使っていれば
Okay, let's do it. Uh-huh!
めったなことじゃ 見つからないよ
But I'll do this alone. Huh?
[TEL]　でも奴ら　常に尾行を 警戒してるから油断すんなよ。
You stay in hiding. Why? It'll go better if we both—
うん　キルアも気をつけて。 チッ…。
Don't forget our main mission!
…ったく　何が 「気をつけて」だよ
Defeating that Chimera Ant.
こっちは 奴らの変化を見極めんのに
That should be your focus.
神経すり減らしてるっつうのに
Let me handle everything else.
大丈夫　バレちゃいない 奴らが俺達の位置に気づけば 行動のどこかに変化が生じる
I'll stir things up. And no offense, but I work more easily alone.
どんなに隠そうとしても
Jeez... Fine, I got it.
ぎこちなさが 顔や　しぐさに必ず表れる
Really? Huh?
こちとら　３つの時から
Do you really understand?
ずっと命懸けの尾行ごっこを させられていたんだ
Killua?
見落とすような マヌケなまねは 絶対にしない！
Promise me you won't make a move!
つけられてる？
Not even if people are killed
right before your eyes!
恐らく…　としか言えねえがな。
Promise!
ヤバい　どんどん 人けのないほうへ移動してる…
Killua? Sorry... It's nothing!
さすがに　もう尾行してることは バレてるかもな…
I'm just a little tense.
それか　まだバレてなくて アジトに戻るのかもしれない
What's this?
だったら この尾行は大成功
They aren't citizens of this country.
罠か…　アジトか…　どっちだ
I would expect a couple of kids to be spies. But they're definitely strong...
罠なら　即脱出 アジトなら　もう少し追う
Are they assassins? Are they here to hunt down the King?
奴らの態度に 不自然なとこはない
Then I can't ignore them...
続行だ！
But I don't want to fight them both at once.
誘いに　のって来ないね。
Just watching him walk, I can tell he's strong.
たぶん　鎖野郎じゃないかもな。 何で？
As much potential as a Squadron Leader?
気配からして 尾行してるのは複数だ。
That kid is something special.
だが　鎖野郎は 恐らく１人で動いてる。 根拠は？ 奴はノストラードファミリーの 人間なわけだろ？
I completely concealed my presence,
but he still sensed something?
組が　かかわってれば 生死を問わず ウボォーは　あらゆる手段で 俺達への脅しに使われる。
How convenient!
しかも 組に報告してねえってことだ。 組に養われてる奴が
Are you sure about this?
組抜きで動いてる理由ってのは 一体　何だ？
You'll really transport my family
and me to another country?
たぶん　私怨だ。
Do not worry.
「たぶん」とか　「恐らく」とか 多くない？
We have received official approval,
and prepared the necessary documents.
うるせぇな　マフィアの後ろ盾抜きで 復讐を考える奴が 他の連中と組むのは　考えづらい。
All that's left is for you to sign the papers.
故に　鎖野郎は単独犯で
However, the condition that you share
your complete knowledge of military affairs
今　俺達を 追ってる奴らとは違う。
in exchange for your freedom is essential.
何か　穴がボコボコの理論だけど。 じゃ　おめぇは　どう思うんだよ！ うん　そうだね…。
As mentioned in the agreement, if you do not keep up your end after signing, we shall both find ourselves in difficult positions.
この追跡者も鎖野郎と かかわりがあると思うけどね。
That won't be a problem.
勘か？
I'll tell you everything...
…ったくよ ひらめきだけの人間に 理論が　どうたら 言われたくねえな。
All I know about the atrocities
that Diego has committed.
どう？　キルア。
We appreciate it.
[TEL]　待ち合わせか俺達を誘ってるか どっちかだな。
Our lives are on the line, as well.
まさか　尾行がバレてんの？
"That Diego has committed"?
[TEL]　五分五分だな でも位置はバレてねえよ。
You talk like it doesn't concern you.
[TEL]　誘いだとしたら　俺達が どこにいるか分かんないから
The wine you're drinking and
the room you stand in
姿を見せろって言いたいわけさ。 [TEL]　どうする？ 待ち合わせの可能性もある。
were earned by following that bastard.
動かず様子を見よう。 [TEL]
You mean "that we've committed,"
you son of a bitch.
注意して見てろ 奴らの顔や　しぐさに 少しでも違和感を感じたら すぐ逃げるぞ。
But I get it... We're here on business.
[TEL]　俺が　ケータイ鳴らしたら 即行脱出だ！　いいな！
So, Marcos-san...
うん　分かった。 [TEL]
Continue going about your business as normal.
[TEL]　フィンクスだ。 おう　何だ？ [TEL] どんな様子かと思ってな。
In two weeks, you and your family
will be relaxing on the beach.
ずっと　つけられてんだけどよ 襲って来ねえんだ。
I can't accept it!
なかなか位置がつかめねえし 長引きそうだな。 [TEL]　それじゃあ いい情報を教えようか？
We're supposed to stand around,
watching as people are killed?
ん？　どういうことだ？
Are you sleepy? Want me to put you to sleep, eh?
ハッ！
If they're gonna check five
million citizens in ten days, simple arithmetic says that's
five hundred thousand per day!
あっ！
Of which one percent will survive! And your point is?
う!!
If we can't draw the three Royal
Guards away from the King, not even the Chairman will
be able to defeat the King.
つぶては布石か 入る！
Thus, we cannot let them discover
our existence before the time is right.
余裕で止めやがった！ 左手１本で！
If that happens, security around the
King will be even further tightened.
う…　うぁ！
You must endure this.
よぉ あっ。
You're telling me to sacrifice five
million to save the human race?
フィンクス 何で　おめぇが　ここにいる？
That's right.
団長と一緒に お出掛けじゃなかったのか？
If blaming me consoles you, go ahead.
ここ４階だぞ…！ 敵をだますには まず味方からだそうだ。
But if you don't have a better idea,
don't be too self-righteous.
くぅ！ また団長にしてやられたよ。
Damn it...
「絶」の達人が多過ぎるとは 思ったんだよなぁ。
We must do only what we can.
二重尾行！　ヒゲと女には 知らされてなかったのか！
But we must put our lives on the line to do so.
さて　にいちゃん
Yeah...
鎖を使う念能力者のことよ。
Is Killua okay?
私達　捜してるの。
He was acting a little weird.
あんた　そいつに頼まれて 私達のこと　つけたんでしょ？
Maybe I should have stuck with him?
知らないよ　俺達は自分の意思で お前達を追ってたんだ。
But if I'd followed him, he'd be mad.
下手なウソは　逆効果だな
You did well to avoid that.
マフィアが　あんた達に 莫大な懸賞金を懸けてるんだ。
How about this?
誰に習った？ 心源流の師範代だよ。
I use my strong tail as a spring,
to propel me among the trees!
問３ 鎖を使う念能力者を知ってるか？ 鎖？
In the darkness, following my
movement is impossible!
お前の師匠ってのが
Caught you!
右手にジャラジャラ 鎖を束ねてるんじゃないのか？ それとも…　お前自身が　そうか？
Now I'm going to crush you!
知らないね 俺の師匠は強化系だし
You're not crushing me!
それに教えてもらったのは 基本の四大行だけだ。 そうか… 知らねえんじゃあ　仕方ねえ。
Huh? I'm the one who caught you!
今　死ぬか　後で死ぬか どっちがいい？ ３秒以内に答えよ。
He seems to have a snake's genes, so he should be able to go ten
days without starving to death.
[TEL]
As I thought... He's strong...
ええ　分かったわ　今行く。
But I should continue to observe.
坊や　お友達は おとなしく　捕まったわよ。
I already let them find me... I need to hide better.
もう一度聞くわ 鎖野郎を知らない？
But it's strange... Why are there soldiers around if the
selection is already finished here?
何度　聞かれても同じだよ 知らない！ そう…　それじゃ　あんたは　どう？
Maybe there are extra guards
because we're near the border.
そこは　まさしく 「幻影旅団」のアジトだった
This time, he's facing two... What will he do?
２人の緊張は 今　極限まで高まっていた
The Chimera Ants are using
darkness to attack Gon.